http://www.mikura.com/privacy-policy

Dubai, United Arab Emirates
Dear Visitor:
http://www.mikura.com "Website" is a site which is operated by Mikura Pearls DMCC and its subsidiaries (collectively, "Mikura Pearls DMCC", "we", "us", "our",) and referred to hereon as “Mikura”. Mikura Pearls DMCC is headquartered in Dubai, United Arab Emirates and having registered address of PO Box 7197, Dubai, United Arab Emirates.
By using this Website, you agree to comply with and to be bound by this Agreement, including the privacy policy described below. Mikura reserves the right to change these terms from time to time at its sole discretion. By using this Website after any such change, you agree to comply with, and be bound by, the terms as changed. Please read this agreement carefully before using this Website.
Mikura grants to you a limited personal, nontransferable, non-sub licensable, revocable, worldwide license to access and make personal, non-commercial use of this Website. Any material from this Website can be used by you for information only and the material cannot be used for any commercial purposes. Mikura reserves any rights not expressly granted by this Agreement.
Sales
- No Resale:
Only those purchasing items for personal use by themselves or as gifts, and not for resale, may order items from this Website. Mikura reserves the right not to sell to any party purchasing items through this Website for the purpose of resale.
- Accuracy:
Mikura strives to ensure that the colors, design, and style of the products that appear on this site reflect those of the actual product. However, variations caused by technical, typographical, digital, or photographic reasons may occur. Mikura will bear no responsibility for errors of any kind. Errors and the consequences of those errors may include, without limitation, any of the following: Product and service descriptions on this Website may vary from time to time, and typographical errors may occur, with the result that product and service descriptions may not be complete, current, or accurate. Any such typographical errors resulting in incorrect product or service information, including incorrect pricing information, may result in the failure to honor an order or request placed by you based on such incorrect information. Because actual colors and the representation you see on this Website will depend on your computer monitor and on other technical factors, Mikura will not guarantee that the display of any products will be accurate at any time.
- Pricing Policy and Online Payment Methods:
Mikura reserves the right to change the prices of products and services featured on this Website at any time, without notice. If you place an order online, you will be charged the price indicated on the Online Store of this Website at the time of your online order. Payment for online orders is processed at the time of ordering. Mikura Pearls accepts Visa, MasterCard and American Express cards via the third party payment processor PayPal. PayPal, Inc. is a leading global online payment processor and uses industry standard encryption and technology to safeguard credit card information. No checks, cash or money-order payments will be accepted for online purchases. An order placed will only be processed and shipped after all the information supplied is deemed verified and payment approval from PayPal has been received.
Existing Mikura gift certificates from any of our stores or retail partners may not be used for online purchases.
- Availability:
Products and services described on this Website are available while supplies last. Mikura reserves the right to discontinue the production of any product, and to discontinue the offering or sale of any product or service at any time, without notice. Mikura will not guarantee that any particular product or service displayed on this Website will be available at any particular location, even if that location has been indicated as a source for that product or service. In the rare case in which an item may become unavailable after you have received confirmation of an order for it, Mikura will contact you, offering you the opportunity to order another item or to cancel your existing order.
Intellectual Property Rights
All materials on this Website, and the Website itself, are protected by copyrights, trademarks and/or other intellectual property rights. These materials are owned by Mikura Pearls DMCC or its subsidiaries or affiliates, or used with permission of their owners. Such materials include, but are not limited to, the photographs, images, illustrations, text, video clips, audio clips, designs, logos, trademarks and other materials contained in this Website, as well as the software used in the design and development of the Website. All rights are reserved, worldwide. The name and mark MIKURA PEARLS and MIKURA, the Mikura logos, the Mikura monogram and all other Mikura-related marks depicted in this Website, whether registered or unregistered, are trademarks or service marks of Mikura Pearls DMCC worldwide including the United States, United Kingdom, Hong Kong, India, United Arab Emirates, Singapore and other countries. Nothing contained herein or on this Website shall be construed as conferring by implication, estoppel, or otherwise any license or right under any patent, copyright, trademark or other intellectual property of Mikura Pearls DMCC or its subsidiaries.
Privacy Policy
We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We want you to know how we use and protect the personal information you give us. This policy ("Privacy Policy") sets out how we use and protect any personal information that you give us when you use this Website, order through our online store, call us or visit any of our stores. If you have any questions about this policy or do not agree with it, please contact our customer services department by email at customer@mikura.com or write to us at PO Box 7197, Dubai, U.A.E. before using this Website. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure you are happy with any changes.
What information do we collect?
In general, you can use this Website without giving us any information. However, additional services may be available if we have certain information about you. We may collect the following information:
account registration information including your name, telephone number, postal address and email address;
billing and shipping information and any other transaction information (should you make a purchase with us);
credit card information (collected, processed and stored by PayPal, Inc.);
if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence; and
information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experiences with our products and contact preferences in order to provide you with further correspondence about our products and services.
What do we do with the information we collect?
We use this information to provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
internal record keeping including but not limited to complying with relevant laws and regulations;
to improve our products and services;
to communicate with you by email, telephone or post if you have ordered or purchased products from us, either regarding the order or purchase or other matters regarding transactions between us or your customer relationship with us;
to communicate with you with regard to your Mikura.com account
to contact you by email, telephone, SMS, MMS or post according to your preferences, in order to share information with you about our products, services and events that may be of interest to you;
Email Marketing
We would also like to provide you with the information above by email. However, we appreciate that email "spam" has become a problem in recent years.
If you are a customer or you have previously asked us for information on our products:
We may contact you regarding your purchase or other matters regarding transactions between us or your customer relationship with us, or send you information on our range of products by email, unless you have asked us not to do so; and
We may also use your email address to share information about our products, services and events that may be of interest to you by way of Mikura Pearls informational emails, unless you have asked us not to do so.
If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive marketing emails from us, please click on the unsubscribe link in the email. Alternatively, you may at any time contact our customer services department by email at customer@mikura.com.
Who do we share this information with?
We will not transfer or disclose your personal information to third parties other than to:
the third party suppliers and vendors we engage to help us run our business;
our affiliates, that is any member of our Group (meaning Mikura Pearls DMCC and its subsidiaries), as defined by applicable local law, in order to process your data for the same purposes or within the same activity as indicated in this Privacy Policy
That is unless we have your permission or are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of Mikura Pearls DMCC, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction within the framework of the relevant data protection law.
How to get copies of or amend the information we have collected?
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you. If you would like a copy of this information, please write to our customer service department at the addresses listed below. If you think any information we have about you is incorrect or incomplete, or you wish to have your details removed from our contact database, similarly please contact our customer services department below and we will correct or update any information as soon as possible.
Customer Services Department
customer@mikura.com
PO Box 7197
Dubai,
U.A.E.
Security and Storage
In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on line. While we use reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your information, we cannot guarantee that electronic commerce is totally secure due to transmission errors, outside events, third party hacking or other causes, and we will not be held responsible for any breach of security unless this is due to our willful failure or gross negligence.
Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.
All information provided through our Website, telephone, catalogue and in store is stored on secure servers. Such information will be processed by staff who work for our group. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfillment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.
Linking
We may link to other websites which are not within our control. When we do this, we will try and make it as clear as possible that you are leaving our Website. We are not responsible for these websites in any way. Once you have left our Website, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Cookies
We use cookies for certain areas of our Website, including but not limited to session cookies, persistent cookies and web beacons. Cookies are files that store information on your hard drive or browser that allow our Website to recognize that you have visited our Website before. They make it easier for you to maintain your preferences on the Website, and by seeing how you use the Website, we can tailor the Website around your preferences and measure usability of the Website. Cookies used by this Website do not contain any personally identifiable information, and we cannot identity a user from his/her cookie unless that user provides personal information voluntarily.
We use cookies to:
Record your session information (such as the particular Products you purchase from our Website);
Record your specific information on the web pages you select to view
You can, should you choose, disable the cookies from your browser and delete all cookies currently stored on your computer. However please note that this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the Website. No information obtained from cookies from which individual customers can be identified will be used by us for marketing purposes.
Conversion Tracking
Search engines offer a feature called “conversion tracking” which is a way to track clicks to sales from either search results or ads on search engines. Using either web beacons or visible images, depending upon the search engine, the search engine notes and saves information in a cookie with non-personal information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. Information is gathered in the aggregate, without unique personal data. Conversion tracking allows the search engine company and Mikura to track clicks to sales, including the number of clicks (“visits”) it takes before a purchase is made and permits us to measure the effectiveness of our search engine participation.
Changes to Policy
Mikura reserves the right to change or update this policy, or any other policy or practice, at anytime, with reasonable notice to users of its website.
Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to our website.
Miscellaneous
- Restrictions on Use:
This Website is protected by United States and international law, including copyright and trademark laws. This Agreement does not grant any license to modify, alter, or frame the materials on this Website that are viewed, downloaded, or otherwise accessed by you. Your license does not include: any right of resale or of commercial use of this Website or its contents; any derivative use of this Website or its contents; or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data-gathering and extraction tools in connection with this Website. You may not remove or alter any proprietary notices, including copyright notices, contained on any downloadable materials, and you must comply with any applicable end-user license agreements. You are also prohibited from posting or transmitting any unlawful, threatening, obscene, libelous, or otherwise offensive material, or engaging in any kind of harassment activity via this Website or any Website linked to it.
Mikura does not represent or warrant that the information contained in this Website is accurate, complete or up-to-date, that this Website is free of defects or that any defects will be remedied. You agree, by using this Website, that your use of this Website is at your sole risk, that you assume full responsibility for all loss of use, loss of data and costs associated with all necessary servicing or repairs of any equipment and/or software that you use in connection with this Website.
- Limitation of Liability:
In no event shall Mikura, any direct or indirect shareholder, affiliate, other related entity, subsidiary, joint venture, partner or their respective shareholders, officers, directors, employees, or agents be liable for any direct, indirect, compensatory, special, incidental, punitive, or consequential damages which may arise, directly or indirectly form access to this website, from the use of it, from the inability to use it, through the downloading of any content (including, without limitation, data, text, images, video or audio from this website) or in connection with any viruses, bugs, action or inaction of any computer system, telephone line, hardware, software or program malfunction or any other error, failure or delay in data transmission or network connection, even if advised of the possibility of that damage. Mikura shall have no liability for the deletion of any communications or information collected, maintained, or transmitted by this Website or the failure to store any information, including personalized settings.
Submissions
Any comments, suggestions, testimonials, endorsements, ideas, or similar material disclosed, submitted or posted by you on this Website or sent to us via electronic or direct mail in connection with it will be considered non-confidential, non-proprietary and not personal either to you or to anyone else. By disclosing, posting, or submitting any such material, you grant to Mikura and its affiliates a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sub-licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, edit, publish, translate, rework, distribute, and display that material without compensation or acknowledgment of source.
Caching, Linking, and Framing by You:
Mikura prohibits caching of any portion of this Website and any unauthorized links to this Website and unauthorized framing of it. Mikura reserves the right to disable any unauthorized links or frames.
- Notices:
All notices and other communications to Mikura shall be in writing, must be given by certified mail, return receipt requested and must be addressed to Mikura at the address set forth for it in this Website at the time of delivery.
- Effect of Waiver or Consent:
A waiver or consent, express or implied, to or of any breach by you, or any delay in enforcement of any provision of this Agreement on the part of Mikura, will not constitute a consent to, or waiver of, any other breach or default by you of the same or any other obligations of you. Failure on the part of Mikura to complain of any act of yours or to declare you in breach or default, irrespective of how long that failure continues, does not constitute a waiver by Mikura of its rights with respect to that default until the applicable statute-of-limitations period has expired.
© 1992-2020 MIKURA
Email Sign-up
Sign Up
Store Locations
Privacy Policy
Sitemap
Careers
Follow Us
